As our first example of using SageMaker,
在第一个 SageMaker 示例中
we're going to take a look at the Boston Housing dataset,
我们将查看 Boston Housing 数据集
and we're going to use that dataset to predict
并使用该数据集
the median cost of a house in the Boston area.
预测波士顿地区的房价中位数
To start with, go into the Tutorials folder and open up the Boston Housing-XGBoost,
首先转到“Tutorials”文件夹并打开 Boston Housing - XGBoost
Batch Transform, High-Level notebook.
(Batch Transform) High-Level notebook
So, that's a mouthful, each of
文件名比较长
these words will make a little more sense as we go through.
当我们继续学习时 将明白这些单词的含义
To start with, Boston Housing is the dataset we're working on,
首先 Boston Housing 表示我们要使用的数据集
and High Level is the API that we're going to be using in this example.
High Level 表示我们将在此示例中使用的 API
Basically, it makes using SageMaker a little easier.
它使 SageMaker 使用起来更简单
First things first, we need to import all of the Python modules we will need,
首先 我们需要导入所需的所有 Python 模块
and that includes all of the SageMaker specific modules.
包括所有的 SageMaker 特定模块
Each of these bits that we import here that come from SageMaker,
对于我们导入的每个 SageMaker 模块
we will talk about in a little more detail later on. All right.
稍后会详细介绍的好的
So, next we get the data,
接下来获取数据
and fortunately for us,
幸运的是
the Boston Housing dataset is provided by sklearn,
Boston Housing 数据集是由 sklearn 提供的
so there's very little to do here,
所以不需要什么操作
we just load the data.
直接加载数据
Now, that the data has been loaded,
数据加载后
we need to split it up into training and testing sets.
我们需要将数据拆分成训练集和测试集
Now, I go one step further here and
另外 我还将训练集
break the training setup into a validation and training set.
拆分成了验证集和训练集
The reason for that is that in this example,
原因是在这个示例中
we are going to use XGBoost as our algorithm of choice,
我们将使用 XGBoost 算法
which is a random tree model.
该算法是一个随机数模型
In my experience, I have found that random tree models are very prone to overfitting,
从我的经验来看 随机数模型很容易过拟合
so having a validation set can improve the results.
所以使用验证集可以改进结果
The way that SageMaker trains and deploys models is the volume.
SageMaker 训练和部署模型的流程如下
To start with, a virtual machine will be
首先创建一个虚拟机
created and it will have all the properties that we wanted to have.
该虚拟机具有所有我们指定的属性
For example, it might come equipped with a GPU,
例如 它可能配有 GPU
or it might have some amount of RAM,
或者具有一定量的 RAM
or some specific number of processors,
或特定数量的处理器
whatever we need for a particular task.
我们针对特定任务指定了这些量
Then, the virtual machine will load an image.
然后 虚拟机将加载镜像
Typically, this image is in the form of a Docker container,
通常 此镜像是一种 Docker 容器
and in our case we'll be using a provided docker container
我们将使用提供的 Docker 容器
which contains the training and inference code to use XGBoost.
其中包含使用 XGBoost 的训练和推理代码
In order for the virtual machine to execute the training code successfully,
为了使虚拟机成功执行训练代码
it needs to access our training data.
它必须能够访问训练数据
SageMaker assumes that this data is available on S3,
SageMaker 认为此数据位于 S3 上
which is Amazon's data storage service.
S3 是 Amazon 的数据存储服务
So, we need to make sure that we upload our datasets there.
我们需要将数据集上传到这里
Fortunately, is very straightforward.
不过步骤很简单
In order to upload our data to S3,
为了将数据上传到 S3
we first have to save that data to a file.
首先需要将数据保存到文件中
Now, here we have chosen to save all of our data inside of
我们选择将所有数据保存到 /data/boston 目录下
the Boston sub-directory of the data directory and make sure that that directory exists,
我们需要确保存在该目录
and then we use Pandas to write our testing, validation,
然后使用 Pandas 将测试 验证和训练集
and training datasets to CSV files in the data directory.
写入 /data 目录下的 csv 文件中
Now, the SageMaker session,
我们目前使用的 SageMaker 会话
which we are currently using that is associated with this notebook instance,
与此 notebook 实例相关联
has associated with it a Python object.
此会话关联了一个 Python 对象
So, here's this session object and if you recall,
这就是 session 对象
if I scroll all the way up in our notebook,
在 notebook 中一直向上滚动
you can recall that we grabbed
我们在这里
this session object using the SageMaker API going back down.
使用 SageMaker API 获取了此 session 对象
So, this session object contains a bunch of useful methods and information.
此 session 对象包含一系列有用的方法和信息
For example, one of the methods that it includes is this upload_data method,
例如 其中一个方法是 upload_data
which given a path to a file and a prefix,
传入文件路径和文件前缀后
uploads this file to the default S3 bucket associated with this session.
它会将这个文件上传到与此会话相关联的默认 S3 存储桶中
So, our notebook instance has a default S3 bucket,
notebook 实例有一个默认的 S3 存储桶
which is like a drive,
就像一个驱动器
and this upload data method uploads a file of our choosing to this drive into a folder,
这个 upload_data 方法将我们所选的文件上传到这个驱动器中的某个文件夹里
which is given by the prefix, which we've set here.
该文件夹由在这里设置的文件前缀指定
So, to go over this again,
再过一遍
the session object contains an upload data method,
session 对象包含一个 upload_data 方法
which uploads a data file to S3 in a bucket,
该方法会将数据文件上传到 S3 存储桶
which is the default bucket for this notebook instance inside of a folder,
该存储桶是此 notebook 的默认存储桶
which is given by the prefix.
并放入由 prefix 指定的文件夹中
Also, it's important to note that the return value of this method is a URI,
此外需要注意的是 这个方法的返回值是一个 URI
which points to that data on S3.
它指向 S3 上的数据
Now that we've downloaded, processed,
我们已经下载 处理
and uploaded our data,
和上传了数据
it's time to start training the model.
下面开始训练模型